const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '123 + 157 =', answer: '280', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '245 + 135 =', answer: '380', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '312 + 168 =', answer: '480', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '861 + 129 =', answer: '990', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '521 + 149 =', answer: '670', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '614 + 176 =', answer: '790', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '341 + 139 =', answer: '480', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '253 + 137 =', answer: '390', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '761 + 129 =', answer: '890', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '411 + 169 =', answer: '580', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];